PROFILE

Digital Channels Manager with Full Stack Web Coding Bootcamp graduation. Lifelong learner recently started to specialize in Javascript, REACT and have interest in Web3. I believe SEO and digital marketing would support with web development.

SAMPLE PROJECTS

Northcoders Backend Project:

https://github.com/muhsinaltintop/muhsinNcGames

Hosted Version of BE:

https://muhsinncgames.herokuapp.com/api

Northcoders Frontend Project:

https://github.com/muhsinaltintop/frontend-nc-gamesmuhsin.git

Deployed Version of FE:

https://front-end-nc-games-muhsinaltintop.netlify.app/

The Little Yellow Duck Project -TLYDP (Northcoders Final Project - BE)

https://github.com/muhsinaltintop/tlydp-api

TLYDP (Northcoders Final Project – FE)

https://github.com/muhsinaltintop/tlydp

TLYDP Video Presentation

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uamsVcRCEbk

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2021 – FEBRUARY 2022

Northcoders

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

13 Weeks Long Bootcamp with an industry-led experience. Learned Javascript Fundamentals, Backend(Node.js, Express, PSQL, APIs), Frontend(DOM, HTML, CSS, REACT), Agile Methodology.

APRIL 2019 – OCTOBER 2021

Odaksan Engineering

Full Stack Digital Marketing

Organized Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, Google Ads and e-mail marketing campaigns. Designed websites with CMS.

EXPERIENCE – UNRELATED

- JULY 2016 JULY 2017 Career Break Due to Political Issues In Turkey
- NOVEMBER 2012 JULY 2016

Gediz University

Research Assistant of International Relations Department

- -Managed department and faculty webpages.
 - AGUST 2009 NOVEMBER 2012

Infomag Publishing

Economics and Business Reporter

-Uploaded website contents of the magazine.

CONTACT

Leicester/The United Kingdom +44 7936 722126

www.muhsinaltintop.com

https://github.com/muhsinaltintop linkedin.com/in/muhsinaltintop/

muhsin.altintop@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS3
- Javascript
- NodeJS
- Exspress
- PSQL
- React
- DART
- Flutter

- WordPress
- Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram Paid Campaings
- Google Ads
- SEO
- Photoshop
- Illustrator

TRAININGS

 Google Project Management: Professional Certificate (Ongoing)

Coursera

Blockchain Specialization (Ongoing)

Coursera

PostgreSQL for Everybody Specialization (Ongoing)
 Coursera

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Northcoders

Introduction to Search Engine Optimization

Coursera

Search Engine Optimization Fundamentals

Coursera

Web Design (HTML – CSS)

GASMEK – (Gaziantep Metropolitan **Municipality** Art and Vocational Education Course)

EDUCATION

Web Design and Coding

Distance Learning, Anadolu University (2020 -)

International Relations

Istanbul Bilgi University (2005-2010)